

TYLER ZEMANTIC

DIGITAL MEDIA DESIGN & MARKETING | tylerzemantic.com



tylerzemantic@uconn.edu



860-450-6983



1 Heritage Rd, Columbia CT, 06237

PROFILE

Passionate and driven marketer with entrepreneurial experience in digital media and marketing. Proficient in problem solving and analytical thinking. Able to find patterns and insigts through numbers and to visalize data while telling a story.

♥ SKILLS

- Social Media
- Content Strategy
- Branding
- Problem Solving
- Digital Marketing
- Analytics & Analysis
- Web Design/Development
- Graphic Design
- Photography
- Video Editing
- Communication
- Project Management

☐ Software Skills

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Hootsuite (Certified)
- Google Analytics (Certified)
- Talkwalker Social **Listening (Certified)**
- Salesforce
- WordPress, Wix, Shopify
- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Microsoft Office/Excel

EDUCATION

University of Connecticut | GPA: 3.52 | Fall 2019

Studied Digital Media and Design with a concentration in business strategies.

School Involvement

The Pound Social Media Analyst AUG 2019 - DEC 2019 **UConn Marketing Society** AUG 2017 - DEC 2019 FEB 2017 - FEB 2019 Huskython Photographer



WORK EXPERIENCE

UConn DMD x Franklin Sports | Social Media Analyst | AUG 2019 - DEC 2019

At the UConn DMD Social Media Analytics Command Center (SMACC) I worked on a team with their social media department at Franklin Sports developing weekly analysis reports. Using programs like Talkwalker, we analyzed data gathered from social media listening to draft statistical narratives.

Aflac | Sales and Marketing Intern | MAY 2019 - AUG 2019

Tracked social media insights and used them to develop reports and work toward creating new public relations strategies. Managed the Capitol Regions Facebook page and created branded content. Met with prospective clients, helped file policies, and continued to check to create meaningful relationships.

T-Mobile | Media Expert | AUG 2017 - JAN 2019

Operated register for cash and credit card transactions. Understood customers wants and needs to sell them the appropriate products and services. Troubleshooted and educated customers about products and services.

Top Runner Marketing | Social Media Specialist | MAR 2016 - AUG 2018

Provided social media insight through developing content strategies and media planning. Managed social channels for clients and developed content for them.